Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Departments, 1985-2006; Series II
  - Business Development
    - Vendor relations
      - Catholic Periodical and Literature Index (CPLI) – Meeting minutes and agreements, correspondence (Restricted for use until 2016 by anyone other than ATLA staff or the Board.), 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Advertising
      - ATLA Ads appearing in College Research Libraries News, 2000 Jan -2001 Feb (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Electronic Products and Services Department
    - Product Support
      - ATLA Religion Database on CD-ROM Handbook, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 141)
      - Ethics Index Brochure, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 142)
      - Ethics Index User's Manual, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 143)
      - Brochures about partner products on CD-ROM; brochure re. International Directory of Theological Training, 1995, no date (Box 3, Folder 144)
      - ATLA Document Delivery Service: Catalog of available journals and order form, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 145)
      - ATLA Document Delivery Service: Catalog of available journals, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 146)
      - ATLA Religion Database on CD-ROM User's Reference, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 147)
      - CD-ROM Database User's Guide, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 148)
      - ATLA Partnership Database on CD-ROM User's Reference, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 149)
      - Letter to customers regarding development of Windows version of ATLA Religion Database on CD-ROM, 1999 Feb (Circa.) (Box 3, Folder 150)
      - Catholic Periodical and Literature Index User's Guide: Installation instructions, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 151)
      - ATLA Religion Database on CD-ROM User's Guide, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 152)
      - Correspondence and contract for the production of the SATB (South African Theological Bibliography), 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 153)
      - Correspondence regarding the SATB (South African Theological Bibliography), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 154)
      - Document Delivery Service brochure for South African Theological Bibliography on CD-ROM (draft); Brochure: South African Theological Bibliography, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 155)
      - Negotiations to produce New Testament Abstracts (NTA), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 156)
      - Agreement to market, publish, distribute and sublicense the Old Testament Abstracts (OTA) Database on CD-ROM, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - Old Testament Abstracts on CD-ROM: Installation Instructions, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      - Dataware upgrade on ATLA's CD-ROM Applications, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 159)
      - NexData work on ATLA Religion Database on CD-ROM, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 160)
      - Brochure about CDRI (Cooperative Digital Resources Initiative), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - ATLAS
      - ATLAS Grant Proposal to the Lilly Endowment, 1999 Mar (Box 4, Folder 162)
      - ATLAS Grant Award from the Lilly Endowment, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 163)
      - Brochure: An Introduction to ATLA Serials, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 610)
  - Financial Services Department
    - Annual audit report, financial statements, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - ATLA Financial Summary, 1992 Sep 1– 1993 Feb 28 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - ATLA Unified Budget, 1993/94 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Financial Statement, 1996 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Financial Statement, 1997 Feb 28 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Financial Report for the period September 1-August 31, 1998 and 1997 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Financial Report for the period November 1998 and 1997, 1998 Dec 23 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Financial Statements, 1999 Aug 31 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Financial Reports for the Year Ending August 31, 1999, 1999 Oct-Nov (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Invoice/Shipping Schedule for 2001- 2002 printed from ATLA Internal Web-Site on 12/2/05 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Index Department
    - Department organization chart and position descriptions (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 11/11/05), 2005 Nov 11 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Menu Pages, Mission and Vision Statements, and Production Schedules (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Dec 2 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Memos regarding Index operations, 1993 Nov (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Summary of IDDO (Index, Database, and Documentation Operations) Strategic Plan Goals FY96, 1995 May (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Sample acceptance and rejection letters for the inclusion of journals in ATLA Indexes, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - "ATLA's Department of Indexes, 2000-2002: An Overview and Future Directions" (Prepared for ATLA Board On-Site Inspection 1/16/03.) (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 11/11/05), 2005 Dec 20 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Minutes of the ATLA Advisory Consultation on the 1900-1948 Indexing Preservation Project, 1991 Feb 6 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - JINPUT (Journal Input Program): IBM Version 3.2: User's Manual, 1991 Dec (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Manual to AIDE 1.50, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Religion Database (RDB) AIDE Input System Documentation, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Index/Database Operations Manual, 1994 Aug 17 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Record Structure and Screen Stats From ARDIS, 2000 (Winter) (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - ARDIS Editing Guide, Revised Edition (pages 1-115) (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Sep 30 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - ARDIS Editing Guide, Revised Edition (pages 116-247) (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Sep 30 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Minimum Level Records Input Guide: Revised February 18, 2005 (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Feb 18 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Reports.jar User's Guide: Draft Edition (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Oct 31 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Journal Evaluation Process and Journal Lists (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Dec 2 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Description of Retrospective Indexing Project (RIP) (Printed from ATLA Intranet on 12/2/05), 2005 Dec 2 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - ATLA Religion Database Advertising Brochure; Biblical Studies subset brochure, 1994,1998? (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Religion Database (RDB) Tagged Record Format 1.2, 1992 Jan 23 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Religion Index MARC Record Specification, Version 2.0, 1997 Mar 25 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - American Theological Library Association Religion Database MARC Record Specification: Version 2.0, 1997 Apr 8 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - American Theological Library Association Religion Database in MARC Record Format Specification: Version 2.12, 1998 Apr 22 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - ATLA Religion Database (RDB) in MARC Format: MARC Record Specifications, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Thesaurus, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Correspondence Regarding Ethics Index, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Journal Titles Indexed in Ethics Index, 1995 Oct (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Comparison of Religion Indices and CD-ROM Local-Area Network Pricing, 1995 Sept and Oct (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Information Sheets Regarding the Creation of ATLAS, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Research in Ministry (RIM), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 23, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 24, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 25, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 26, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 27, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 28, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 29, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 30, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 31, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 32, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 33, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 34, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 35, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Volume 36, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 32, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 33, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 34, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 35, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 36, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Religion Index One: Periodicals: Semiannual Edition: Volume 37, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Religion Index Two (RIT) Index Production Software, 1996 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Religion Index Two (RIT) Documentation: 3rd Draft, 1997 Jan 20 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Religion Index Two: Multi-Author Works, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR) Manual: Draft, 1997 Jun 20 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 245)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 246)
    - Index to Book Review in Religion (IBRR), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 247)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Sample Copy of Index, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Multi-Author Works, with supplement, 1991 Oct 18-1992 Feb 7 (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Interim Progress Report, 1991 Jan 15 (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Interim Progress Report, 1992 Jan (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Interim Progress Report, 1992 Jun (Box 9, Folder 253)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Proposed Changes, 1991 Jan (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Program (ICLDP), Updates on Progress for the Editorial Advisory Committee, 1991 Jul-1992 Jan (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Budget Materials, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), System Development Meetings, 1991 Nov-1992 Nov (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Classification Schedule Revisions, 1991 (Mostly) (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Final Advisory Committee Meeting, 1992 Aug-Oct (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Final Action Plan and Schedule, 1991 Jan-1992 Nov (Box 9, Folder 260)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Emory University, Pitts Theology Library On-Site Indexing, 1990 Mar-1992 Jan (Box 9, Folder 261)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Graduate Theological Union On-Site Indexing, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 262)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Princeton Theological Seminary On-Site Indexing, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 263)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Union Theological Seminary in New York On-Site Indexing, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Yale On-Site Indexing, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Correspondence With Free-Lance Indexer Virginia Neely, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Correspondence, 1992 Feb-1993 Sep (Box 9, Folder 267)
    - International Christian Literature Documentation Project (ICLDP), Brochure, 1993? (Box 9, Folder 268)
    - Index Inventory, 1991 June? (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Correspondence related to acceptance of various journals for indexing, 1991-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1-23)
  - Information Services Department
    - Information Services Pages From ATLA Internal Web-Site (Printed from ATLA Internal Web-Site on 12/2/05), 2005 Dec 2 (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - Babylon Software Requirements, 1996 Fall (Box 9, Folder 271)
    - Correspondence Regarding a Spanish-Language Demonstration CD-ROM, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 272)
    - Report on CUADRASTAR Users Meeting, 1998 Nov 5 (Box 9, Folder 273)
    - ATLA Sampler CD-ROM (Printed "snapshots" from disc), 2001 Mar (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Member Services Department
    - General
      - Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 275)
      - Office Procedures Manual, 1994 Oct (Box 9, Folder 276)
      - Annual Report of the Director of Members Services, 1993 Jun -1994 May (Box 9, Folder 277)
      - Budget Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 278)
      - Budget Request for 1994/95 Fiscal Year, 1994 Apr 27 (Box 9, Folder 279)
      - Request for Information on Library Development, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 280)
      - Library materials Exchange Procedures, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 281)
      - Brochure for the Management Issues Seminar: "The Library Budget", 2001 Jul (Box 9, Folder 282)
      - Brochure for Professional Development Seminars: "Instructional Design for Librarians," and "Practical Personnel Management for the Theological Librarian", 2002 Jun (Box 9, Folder 283)
      - Brochure Recommendations for Annual Giving Fund, also a list of registration fees paid from the fund, 1992 Jul (Box 9, Folder 284)
      - Appeal for Scholarships and Grants Fund Contributions, 2005 Nov 1 (Box 9, Folder 285)
      - Library Materials Exchange prorgram - planning correspondence, procedures, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Memberships
      - Membership Brochures, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 286)
      - Student Membership Brochure, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 287)
      - Individual and Student Membership Brochure, 2003 Oct (Box 9, Folder 288)
      - Individual and Student Membership Brochures (Box 9, Folder 289)
      - Brochures aimed at attracting Student Members, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 290)
      - Institutional Membership Brochure, 2003 Oct (Box 9, Folder 291)
      - Institutional Membership Brochure, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 292)
      - Institutional Memberships, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 293)
      - International Institutional Membership Brochure, 2003 Oct (Box 9, Folder 294)
      - Affiliate Membership Brochure, 2003 Oct (Box 9, Folder 295)
      - Affiliate Membership Brochure, 2003 Dec (Box 9, Folder 296)
      - Affiliate Membership Brochure, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 297)
      - Membership Statistics, 1985-1995 (Box 9, Folder 298)
      - Correspondence Regarding Mailing Lists, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 299)
      - Membership Directory, 1994 Sep 22 (Box 9, Folder 300)
      - Membership Directory, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 301)
      - Membership Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - Annual Conference
      - Proceedings: 50th – Denver (See also RG 163 for programs and proceedings through 1998), 1996 (Box 9, Folder 303)
      - Program: 51st - Boston, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 304)
      - Proceedings: 51st - Boston, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 305)
      - Program: 52nd – Leesburg, VA, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 306)
      - Proceedings: 52nd – Leesburg, VA, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 307)
      - Proceedings: 53rd - Chicago, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 308)
      - Proceedings: 54th - Berkeley, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 309)
      - Proceedings: 55th- Durham, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 310)
      - Program: 56th – St. Paul, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 311)
      - Proceedings: 56th – St. Paul, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 312)
      - Program: 57th - Portland, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 313)
      - Proceedings: 57th - Portland, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 314)
      - Program: 58th - Kansas City, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 315)
      - Proceedings: 58th - Kansas City, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 316)
      - Program: 59th - Austin, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 317)
      - Proceedings: 59th - Austin, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 318)
      - Proceedings: 59th - Austin, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 319)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 59th Annual Conference, 2005 Jun 15-18 (Box 10, Folder 320)
      - Summary of Proceedings: 59th Annual Conference, 2005 Jun 15-18 (Box 10, Folder 321)
      - Conference Software, Badge-O-Magic User's Guide, Invoices, and Sample Printout, 1989-1993 Apr (Box 10, Folder 322)
      - Managing Financial Information in Libraries (Records of Presenter Mary Bischoff), 1990 Jun (Box 10, Folder 323)
      - Handbook for Conferences of the American Theological Library Association (Draft of June 1991 Revision), 1991 Jun (Box 10, Folder 324)
      - Meeting of Women Library Directors, held at the 1991 ATLA Conference (Records of Meeting Organizer Mary Bischoff) (Box 10, Folder 325)
      - Registration Packet for the 45th ATLA Conference, Toronto, 1991 Mar (Box 10, Folder 326)
      - Materials From Conference Packet: 46th, 1992 Jun 17-20 (Box 10, Folder 327)
      - Registration Form, Preliminary Program, and Miscellaneous Handouts: 46th, 1992 Jun 17-20 (Box 10, Folder 328)
      - Conference Planning Documents for the 47th (1993) ATLA Annual Conference, 1990 Jul -1993 June (Box 10, Folder 329)
      - Conference Planning Correspondence, 47th (1993) ATLA annual Conference, 1993 Jan-May (Box 10, Folder 330)
      - 1993 ATLA Annual Conference Registration Packet: 47th, 1993 Jun 16-19 (Box 10, Folder 331)
      - Correspondence With Cassandra Brush About Membership and Attendance at Annual Conference, 1993 Sep – 1994 Aug (Box 10, Folder 332)
      - Evaluations of 1994 ATLA Conference (Box 10, Folder 333)
      - Evaluations of the 1998 ATLA Annual Conference, 1998 Jun 18-20 (Box 10, Folder 334)
      - Evaluations of the 1998 ATLA Annual Conference, 1998 Jun 18-20 (Box 10, Folder 335)
      - 55th Annual Conference Attendee Confirmation Packet, 2001 Jun (Box 10, Folder 336)
      - 56th Annual Conference Attendee Confirmation Packet, 2002 Jun (Box 10, Folder 337)
      - Planning Meetings for the 2003 ATLA Conference, Agenda Items, 2002 Oct 11-13 (Box 10, Folder 338)
      - 57th Annual Conference Attendee Confirmation Packet, 2003 Jun (Box 10, Folder 339)
      - Brochure for Professional Development Seminar, "The Theological Library and the Educational Enterprise", 2003 Jun (Box 10, Folder 340)
      - 58th Annual Conference Attendee Confirmation Packet, 2004 Jun (Box 10, Folder 341)
      - 59th Annual Conference Attendee Confirmation Packet, 2005 Jun (Box 10, Folder 342)
      - 59th Annual Conference Packet, 2005 Jun (Box 10, Folder 343)
      - Handbook for Conferences, 2000 Oct (Box 10, Folder 344)
      - Handbook for Conferences, 2001 & 2004 (Box 10, Folder 345)
      - Exhibitor Prospectuses, 1996-2002, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 346)
      - Exhibitor Confirmation Packet, 2001 Jun 20-21 (Box 10, Folder 347)
      - Exhibitor Confirmation Packet, 2002 Jun 20-21 (Box 10, Folder 348)
      - Exhibitor Confirmation Packet, 2003 Jun 26-27 (Box 10, Folder 349)
      - Exhibitor Confirmation Packet, 2004 Jun 17-18 (Box 10, Folder 350)
      - Exhibitor Prospectus, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - Member Publications
      - Newsletter Index for vols. 41-45, (1993/94-1997/98) (Box 10, Folder 352)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 38, nos. 1-4, 1990 Aug 18–1991 May 18 (Box 10, Folder 353)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 39, nos. 1- 4, 1991 Aug 17 -1992 May 16 (Box 10, Folder 354)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 40, nos. 1-2, 1992 Aug 15 and Nov 14 (Box 10, Folder 355)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 40, no. 3, 1993 Feb 13 (Box 10, Folder 356)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 40, no. 4 [Includes Index for vols. 36-40 (1988/89-1992/93)], 1993 May 15 (Box 10, Folder 357)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 41, no. 1, 1993 Aug 14 (Box 10, Folder 358)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 41, no. 2, 1993 Nov 13 (Box 10, Folder 359)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 41, no. 3, 1994 Feb 12 (Box 10, Folder 360)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 41, no. 4, 1994 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 361)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 42, nos. 1-4, 1994 Aug 13- 1995 May 13 (Box 10, Folder 362)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 43, no. 1, 1995 Aug 12 (Box 10, Folder 363)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 43, no. 2, 1995 Nov 11 (Box 11, Folder 364)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 43, nos. 3-4, 1996 Feb 10, May 11 (Box 11, Folder 365)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 44, nos. 1-4, 1996 Aug – 1997 May (Box 11, Folder 366)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 45, nos. 1-5, 1997 Aug, 1997 Nov, 1998 Feb-Aug (Box 11, Folder 367)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 46, nos. 1-4, 1998 Nov -1999 Aug (Box 11, Folder 368)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 47, nos. 1-4, 1999 Nov -2000 Aug (Box 11, Folder 369)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 48, nos. 1-4, 2000 Nov -2001 Aug (Box 11, Folder 370)
      - Newsletters, Vol. 49, nos. 1-3, 2001 Nov- 2002 May (Box 11, Folder 371)
      - Newsletters, Vol. 49, no. 4, 2002 Aug (Box 11, Folder 372)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 50, no. 1-4, 2002 Nov -2003 Aug (Box 11, Folder 373)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 51, nos. 1-4, 2003 Nov -2004 Aug (Box 11, Folder 374)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 52, nos.1-4, 2004 Aug – 2005 Nov (Box 11, Folder 375)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 53, nos. 1-2, 2006 Feb, Nov (Box 11, Folder 376)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 53, no. 2, 2006 Feb (Box 11, Folder 377)
      - Newsletter, Vol. 53, nos. 3,4, 2006 May, August (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Duplicate copies of Newsletters, vol. 41-50, 1994-2003 (Box 15, Folder 1-10)
      - Correspondence regarding Newsletter mailing list, 1993 Jul (Box 11, Folder 378)
      - ATLA Advertising Rates for Association Newsletter, 1995? (Box 11, Folder 379)
      - Product News, 2003 May -2004 May (Box 11, Folder 380)
      - Product News, 2004 May (Box 11, Folder 381)
      - Catalog: Publications, Programs, and Services, 1990-91 (Box 11, Folder 382)
      - Catalog, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 383)
      - Catalog, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 384)
      - Catalog, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 385)
      - Catalog, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 386)
      - Catalog, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 387)
      - Catalog, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 388)
      - Catalog, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 389)
      - Catalog, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 390)
      - Catalog, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 391)
      - Catalog, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 392)
      - Catalog, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 393)
      - Program Notes (re: Preservation and Indexes programs) (Incomplete), 1991 Apr -1995 Dec (Box 11, Folder 394)
      - ATLA Logos, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 395)
      - Essays in Celebration of the First Fifty Years, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 396)